Guide to the Willard Dickerman Straight papers, 1825-1925.
Straight, Willard Dickerman papers, 1825-1925.
- Visual Materials
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - Ceremonies 1909 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - China, Peking 1909 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - Empress Dowager, Tz'u His 1909 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Funeral Procession of the Empress Dowager
    - Funeral of Empress Dowager 1909 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - Residence, Peking 1911 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1911 c. (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - Architecture, Interior 1911 c. (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1911c. (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - China, Peking 1912 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Peking, Rebellion of 1912 1912 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Street Scenes 1912 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - China, Peking 1912 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Peking, Rebellion of 1912 1912 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Street Scenes 1912 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Arches 1912 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - British Army 1912 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Calhoun, William J. 1912 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - China, Peking 1912 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Peking, Rebellion of 1912 1912 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - U.S. Army 1912 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - China, Peking 1912 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Gates 1912 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Peking, Rebellion of 1912 1912 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Street Scenes 1912 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Peking, Rebellion of 1912 1912 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Peking in Ruins (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1912 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Peking in Ruins (annotated)
    - U.S. Army 1912 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - China, Peking 1912 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - Peking, Rebellion of 1912 1912 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - U.S. Army 1912 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Bowditch, Peter 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Churches 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Landscapes 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Palaces 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Philippines, Manila 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Manila (annotated)
    - Village Scenes 1912 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Saigon
    - Boats n.d. (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Saigon
    - Botanical Garden, Saigon n.d. (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Saigon
    - Indo-China, Saigon n.d. (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Saigon
    - Transportation, Carts n.d. (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Saigon
    - Transportation, Jinrikshas n.d. (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - Korea n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - Lumber n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - Mines n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Koreans n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - Railroads n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - Seoul Fusan Railroad n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korea (annotated)
    - Transportation, Railroads n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Korean (annotated)
    - Industry n.d. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - City Scenes n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Coal Hill, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Palaces n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Princess Tomb n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Roofs n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Summer Palace n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - U.S. Legation, Peking n.d. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - Architecture, Interior 1911-1912 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1911-1912 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Peking Home (annotated)
    - Residence, Peking 1911-1912 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Java
    - Java, Batavia 1909 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Java
    - Java, Buitenzorg 1909 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Java
    - Landscapes 1909 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Java
    - Occupations 1909 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Java
    - River Scenes 1909 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Java
    - Vendors 1909 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Java Scenes
    - Botanical Gardens, Buitenzorg, Java 1909 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Java Scenes
    - Java, Buitenzorg 1909 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Java Scenes
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1909 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Java Scenes
    - Seascapes 1909 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Java Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1909 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Java Scenes
    - Vendors 1909 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Straight and Friends
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Calhoun, Lucy 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Calhoun, William J. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - China, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Residence, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Straight, Willard D. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Transportation, Sedan Chairs 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Straights and Friends
    - U.S. Legation, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Polo in China (annotated, sketch)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1907 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Polo in China (annotated, sketch)
    - Polo 1907 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Polo in China (annotated, sketch)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Polo in China (annotated, sketch)
    - Marvin, George D. 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Polo in China (annotated, sketch)
    - Sports 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Polo in China (annotated, sketch)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - Architecture, Interior 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - C.E. Lemunyon, Peking and Tientsin, China 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - Calhoun, William J. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - Portraits 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - Transportation, Carriages 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - Tsai, T'Ing-Kan 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight in China (annotated)
    - U.S. Legation, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Peking Friends and Associates
    - Architecture, Exterior 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates
    - Calhoun, Lucy 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates
    - Calhoun, William J. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates
    - China, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates
    - U.S. Legation, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Westerners 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Portraits 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Residence, Peking 1909-1911 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Straight and Friends
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straight and Friends
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straights and Friends
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straights and Friends
    - French, Charles n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Ice Skating n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Social Life n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Straight, Dorothy W. n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Straight, Willard D. n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Winter Scenes n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1911 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Portraits 1911 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Residence, Peking 1911 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1911 c. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Casenave, Maurice 1911c. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1911c. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Menocal, Beatrice De 1911c. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Peking Friends and Associates (annotated)
    - Menocal, Daniel A. De 1911c. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Dorothy Whitney Straight
    - China, Peking 1912 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Whitney Straight
    - People, Individual Westerners 1912 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Whitney Straight
    - Portraits 1912 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Whitney Straight
    - Architecture, Interior 1912 c. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Whitney Straight
    - Dress 1912c. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Whitney Straight
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1912c. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Paddock, Gordon 1912 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - People, Identified Groups of Westerners 1912 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1912 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Portraits 1912 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Railroads 1912 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Social Life 1912c. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1912c. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1912c. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1912c. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Westerners in China (annotated)
    - Winter Scenes 1912c. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Calhoun, Lucy n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Corbett, May n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Kung, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - People, Identified Groups n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - P'U-Lun, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Su Kung, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Tsai Hsun, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Tsai Tze, Duchess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Groups of Women, Chinese and Western
    - Women n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Calhoun, William J. 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Casenave, Maurice 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - China, Peking 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - French, Charles 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Hsu, Ting-Lin 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - People, Groups 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Portraits 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - P'U-Lun, Princess 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - T'Ang, Shao-Yi 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Tsai, T'Ing-Kan 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Kung, Prince 1911 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - Calhoun, William J. 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - Casenave, Maurice 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - French, Charles 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - Gatrell, Thomas J. 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - People, Groups 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - People, Individuals 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - Portraits 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight and Associates (annotated)
    - Tsai, T'Ing-Kan 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Portraits (annotated)
    - People, Identified Individuals 1904 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Portraits (annotated)
    - Portraits 1904 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Portraits (annotated)
    - Powkee, Shanghai and Nanking, China 1904 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Portraits (annotated)
    - K. Ogawa, Tokyo, Japan 1904, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Portraits (annotated)
    - Murata 1904, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - People, Identified Individual Chinese 1907 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Photograph Artistic, Japan 1907 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Portraits 1907 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - C. Araki 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Chen, Chao-Chung 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Chou, Shu-Mo 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Dress 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Takebayashi, Tokyo, Japan 1907c. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Straights and Friends
    - China, Peking 1909c (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Great Wall 1909c. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1909c. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Straight, Willard D. 1909c. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Straights and Friends
    - Transportation, Sedan Chairs 1909c. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Straights and Friends
    - U.S. Legation, Peking 1909c. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - Dress n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - Hsu, Ting-Lin n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - People, Individuals n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - P'U-Lun, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - T'Ang, Shao-Yi n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Friends and Associates
    - Women n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Women
    - Cheng San Photographer n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Women
    - Dress n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Women
    - Kolmakova, Viadivostok, Russia n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Women
    - Kung, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Women
    - People, Identified Individual Chinese n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Women
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Women
    - Tsai Tze, Duchess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Women
    - Women n.d. (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - People, Identified Individual Chinese 1910 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Portraits 1910 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Dress 1910c. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - His-Liang 1910c. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - Sze-Yuen-Ming, Shanghai, China 1910c. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Chinese Officials (annotated, autographed)
    - T'Ang, Shao-Yi 1910c. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondent
    - Collins, Robert M. 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondent
    - Kuroki, General 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondent
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondent
    - Russo-Japanese War 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - Ebuchi 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - Furuya 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - Hayashi 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - K. Iwata, Seoul, Korea 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - K. Murakami, Seoui, Korea 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - Korea, Seoul 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - Oyama 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - People, Identified Individuals 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - Portraits 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - S. Fujita, Seoul, Korea 1904-1905 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Japanese officials in Korea (annotated, autographed)
    - Hagiwara, S. 1904-1907 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Mukden (annotated)
    - Portraits 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - Arnell, Charles J. 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - Fairchild, Nelson 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - Gillis, J.V. 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - Marvin, George D. 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - Takeyuch Photographer, Habarovsk, Russia 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Mukden (annotated, autographed)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1906-1908 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Calhoun, Lucy 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Calhoun, William J. 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Casenave, Maurice 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Cordes, Henry 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Gatrell, Thomas J. 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Hillier, E.G. 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Menocal, Beatrice De 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Menocal, Daniel A. De 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Portraits 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Purple Cows 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Peking (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1909-1912 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Cheng San Photographer n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Children n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Dress n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Hao, Madame n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Kung, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - People, Identified Groups of Chinese n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - P'U-Lun, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Tsai Hsun, Princess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Tsai Tze, Duchess n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - U.S. Legation, Peking n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Chinese Women (annotated)
    - Women n.d. (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - A.B. Cross, Salem, Massachusetts 1875-1878 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Beardsley, Oswego, New York 1875-1878 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Portraits 1875-1878 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Straight, Emma D. 1875-1878 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Straight Family
    - Dickerman, Willard A. 1885 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Straight Family
    - Portraits 1885 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Straight Family
    - B.S. Alford, Oswego, New York 1885 c. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Straight Family
    - Beard, N.C. (Mrs.) 1885 c. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Straight Family
    - J.A. Scholten, St. Louis, Missouri 1885c. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Straight Family
    - O. Monroe, Dunkirk, New York 1885c. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight, Henry H. 1885c. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Baldwin Coolidge, Boston Massachusetts 1880-1897 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Lovell, Oswego, New York 1880-1897 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Oliver, Oswego, New York 1880-1897 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Portraits 1880-1897 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. 1880-1897 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight